

## **PROFILE**

Over 10 years of experience as a Design Entrepreneur & Styling Consultant in the Fashion Industry today, I am driven to crafting meaningful digital experiences. I have recently graduated from the Master's Program in Web & New Media Design from the Academy of Art University, San Francisco.

I bring a passion for interactive storytelling & user-centered design thinking. I am self motivated with an aptitude for team collaboration, open communication & persistent problem-solving. I bring both analytical and out-of-the box creative solutions to the design task. An entrepreneurial attitude keeps me motivated through the obstacles.

### **EXPERIENCE**

2014 | CONTRACT WEB DESIGNER MYLO SOLUTIONS, SAN FRANCISCO

Over a period of six weeks, I redesigned the logo and the company website. I worked closely with the Business Development and the Marketing team to communicate the company message effectively.

2013 I USABILITY TESTING FACILITATOR ACADEMY OF ART UNIVERSITY, SAN FRANCISCO

Facilitate usability tests of digital interfaces between the designer and the user. Assist the designer in crafting task flows and testing documents for the test.

2013 | TECHNOLOGIST/ STUDENT PARTICIPANT FLY GARAGE, MONDELEZ

Fly Garage is an innovation incubator hosted by Mondelez. Over a period of 10 days, I collaborated with creatives from all over the world to brainstorm on innovative solutions for brand engagement.

2012 | CONTRIBUTING WRITER DIGITALSTYLEDIGEST.COM, SAN FRANCISCO

As a contributing writer at Digital Style Digest, I explored, researched and reported on the current happenings in the world of fashion tech.

2007-2013 I CO-FOUNDER & CREATIVE DIRECTOR POP-ATT, MUMBAI, INDIA

Pop-Att is a fashion and lifestyle brand selling across India. We designed, manufactured and distributed products designed for the young adult female audience. Being an entrepreneur while I was hands on with all aspects of the business, primarily I was involved in product development, business strategy and marketing.

2001-2010 I FOUNDER & CREATIVE DIRECTOR STYLE MIND SOUL, INDIA

Over a decade I worked with advertising agencies, international brands, fashion publications and feature films as a Fashion Styling Consultant on their press and film shoots. I managed a team of Junior Stylist and wardrobe coordinators.

1999-2001 | FASHION STYLIST, ELLE MAGAZINE, INDIA

In fulfilling the role of a Fashion Stylist, I collaborated with the Fashion Editor to scout the latest talent in the fashion business and work with a team of photographers, make-up & hair stylist, models to create original visual content for the monthly issue of the magazine.

## **SKILLS**

**DESIGN TOOLS** 

Adobe Creative Suite Omnigraffle, Balsamiq Web based prototyping tools Usability testing Facilitation

TECHNOLOGY HTML5, CSS3,

jQuery, Javascript
MOTION GRAPHICS

Adobe After Effects Cinema 4D

### **EDUCATION**

2014 I M.F.A WEB & NEW MEDIA DESIGN Academy of Art University, San Francisco

2001 | B.F.A FASHION DESIGN CEPZ Institute of Fashion Technology Mumbai, India

# INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

- Fashion
- Retail
- Publishing
- Advertising
- Films
- Technology